Guide to the Western Pennsylvania Conservancy Records and Photographs, 1885-2006 AIS.1999.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1885-2006; 1950-2004; II.
  - Community Garden Program, 1975-2006; 1988-2004; 2.
    - II. Reizenstein School; Hill District; 40th Street Bridge; Brighton Road and Charles Street; and South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - JJ. Bridgeville, South; and Claysville, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - KK. O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street; White Oak; Clairton; Weil Elementary School; Webster Avenue and Kirkpatrick Street; Carnegie/Mansfield; and Castle Shannon Boulevard, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - LL. Johnstown; and Clarion, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - MM. Dormont Avenue; 22/30/60 Interchange; Wenzell Avenue and Broadway Avenue; Greenfield, Lower; Hazelwood Avenue, Beechwood Boulevard, and Saline Street; Allegheny River Boulevard; and East Liberty, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - NN. Slippery Rock; South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; Butler; and Kennedy Township, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - OO. 5700 Butler Street; Linden Elementary School; Downtown Greening; Downtown Hanging Baskets; and Point State Park, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - PP. McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; Shaler Intermediate Academy; Hollidaysburg; State College; 15th Street and Tyrone; 11th Street and Tyrone; and Slippery Rock, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - QQ. Beaver; Butler; and Rochester, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - RR. Butler; WPC Building; and Faith's Garden, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Stanhope Street, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - A. McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; Carson Street and Sarah Street; and Riverfront Park Circle, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - B. Riverfront Park Circle; General Robinson Street; Greeley Avenue and Josephine Avenue; and Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - C. Route 22 and Route 48; Slippery Rock; and Sewickley Hanging Baskets, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - D. Haymaker Extension; Swissvale; and Highland Park, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - F. Route 885 and Glass Run Road; McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; Fort Pitt Tunnel; and East Avenue and 6th Street, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - G. Reizenstein School; Route 22 and Route 48; and Aliquippa, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - H. McKees Rocks Bridge; Marshall Avenue and California Avenue; and Oliver High School, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - I. Brighton Road and Charles Street; Canal Street and Cedar Avenue; Homer Street and Walz Avenue; Spring Garden; North Shore Drive; and North Avenue and Brighton Road, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 37)
    - J. 11th Street and Carson Street; Barry Street and Josephine Avenue; Greeley Street and Josephine Avenue; Carson Street and Sarah Street; Riverview Park; and Perrysville Avenue and Federal Street, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 38)
    - K. Reizenstein School; Baum Boulevard and Penn Circle; Penn Circle and Penn Avenue; and Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - L. Route 885 and Glass Run Road; Grant Street; and McArdle Roadway and Grandview Avenue, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - M. Liberty Avenue and Commonwealth Place; Gateway Center, Faith's Garden; Stanhope Street; Ivory Avenue and Evergreen Road; One Heinz Street, Sarah Heinz House; and Arlington Avenue and McArdle Roadway, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 57, Folder 41)
    - N. Stanhope Street; Dormont Avenue; Swissvale; Edgewood; Squirrel Hill Tunnel; Greenfield, Lower; Greenfield, Upper; and Morrowfield Avenue, Tilbury Street and Beechwood Boulevard, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 57, Folder 42)
    - O. Etna; Hope Hollow Road; Crescent Elementary School; Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; Linden Avenue and McPherson Boulevard; Linden Avenue and Thomas Boulevard; Shady Lane School; and Morrowfield Avenue, Tilbury Street, and Beechwood Boulevard, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 57, Folder 43)
    - P. Allderdice High School; Penn Avenue and Friendship Avenue; Castle Shannon Boulevard; Fort Pitt Tunnel; Hazelwood Avenue, Saline Street, and Beechwood Boulevard; Forbes Avenue and South Dallas Avenue; and South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 57, Folder 44)
    - Q. Kirkpatrick Street and Fifth Avenue; 1835 Forbes Avenue; Centre Avenue and Dinwiddie Street; Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue; Weil Elementary School; 48th Street and Butler Street; and 57th Street and Butler Street, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 57, Folder 45)
    - R. Route 48 and Haymaker Extension; Route 48 and Lincoln Highway; O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street; Route 837 and Maple Avenue; Concord Elementary School; Brownsville Road and Margaret Street; Brownsville Road and Wynoka Avenue; and Noblestown Road and Durbin Street, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - R1. South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; Anderson Street Bridge; Mifflin School; Beechwood Elementary School; Rankin Bridge; Homestead Grays Bridge; and Swissvale, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - S. Route 62 and State Street; Route 19 and West North Street; Route 19 and East Butler Street; and Farrell, Pa., 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - S1. Brentwood Middle and High School; Forbes Avenue at Carnegie Museum; Squirrel Hill Tunnel; Fort Pitt Tunnel; Polish Hill; 40th Street Bridge; Steuben Street and Middletown Road; and Fifth Avenue and Kirkpatrick Street, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - T. Hope Hollow Road and Route 50; Wabash Street and Neptune Street; Route 909 and Hilton Road; Route 356 and Tarentum Bridge; Route 48 and Haymaker; Route 48 and Haymaker Extension; Route 910 and Saxonburg Road; Route 30 and Greengate Road; and Tri-Boro Expressway and Electric Avenue, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - U. Kennedy Township; Moon; Montour Run Road; 22/30/60 Interchange; Lydia Street; Mansfield; Scott/Carnegie Interchange; Greentree; and Mercer, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - V. Route 18 and Broadway Street; Route 51 and Colerain; Brownsville Road and Maple; McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; Ohio Street and Grant Avenue; Shaler Intermediate School; and West Deer, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - W. Route 286 and Indian Spring; Route 66 and Route 322; Route 906 and Tyrol; Route 68 and Hansen; and Route 422 and Route 8, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - X. Liberty Avenue; Millvale; Hays; Castle Shannon Boulevard; Johnstown; and Hollidaysburg, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Y. Connellsville; Meadville Triangle; Meadville School; Oil City Gateway and Fountain; and Franklin, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Z. 11th Street; 15th Street and Lincoln; Route 40 and Broadway; I79 Northbound, Southbound, and Welcome Center; I70 Welcome Center; and Route 21 and Route 19, 2004; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Duplicates, 2004-2006; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Personnel and Related Activities, 1955-2003; 3.
    This subseries contains prints, negatives, and slides of people and related activities. The images in this subseries document events, such as luncheons, staff parties, WPC outings, and Members Day; staff members and the general public; activities, including fishing, boating, and skiing; and presentations, including slide shows given at various speaking engagements.
    - Arizona School Garden Conference, Presentation; Chicago School Garden Symposium, Presentation; Department Planting at Reizenstein School, Presentation; Phoenix School Garden Conference, Presentation; SGI Fall Garden Swap, Presentation, 1998-2002; Slides (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Allegheny County Greenways, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Alex Bellotti, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Alex Bellotti, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Community Garden Program, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Floral Beds and Plantings, Presentation; Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Flowers, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Garden Shots, Presentation, 2003; Slides (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Gateway Gardens Parkway, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - People and Outdoor Activities, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Speaking About the Western Pennsylvania Conservancy, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Spring, Presentation, 2001; Slides (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Staff Members and Annual Meetings, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Three Rivers Parkway and UAD Architects, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Titles and Graphics, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - WPC Introduction, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Westmoreland Water Authority Acquisition, Woods Stock Photography, Presentation, Slides (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Allegheny River Corridor Project, 1971; Prints (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Award Ceremony held by the WPC, 2002; Prints (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Boats and Boating, 1965-1975; Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Canoeing Trip, Photographs from Sayre and Jean W. Rodman, Prints (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Clarion, Pa., Luncheon, Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Dr. Otto E. Jennings, Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Don Whitlatch Wildlife Painting, "Sunrise at Roaring Run", About 1973; Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Don Whitlatch Wildlife Painting Membership Drive, Copy Artwork, About 1973; Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Fishing, Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Fishing, Camping, and Canoeing, Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Fishing and Canoeing, Prints (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - French Creek, 1998; Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Glacial Lakes at Edinboro University, April 1, 2000; Prints (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Halloween, Prints (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - JCO Personnel, Studio Portraits, Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Linking Families, Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Members Day, Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Members Day, 1996-1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Members Day, 1998-1999; Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Members Day, 2000; Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Members Day at Bear Run, Prints (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Members Day, Clarion River and Youghiogheny River, Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Members Day, Cook Forest Hike, Prints (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Members Day, Wildflower Walk at Raccoon Creek State Park, 1998; Prints (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - National Park Tour, B/W Negatives (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - National Wildlife Federation Award, About 1966; Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Nature Link at McKeever, August 25-27, 2000; Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Nature Link, 2000; Mini Digital Video Cassette, Negatives (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Nature Club Outings, About 1966; Prints (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Newsletter Copy Prints, Prints and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Newspaper Clipping of W. Galen Barron images, The Pittsburgh Press Sunday Roto, October 16, 1966; Prints (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Newspaper Clipping, Frank M. Hull images, The Pittsburgh Press Sunday, July 21, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Peer Review, Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - People, Between 1955-1975; Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - People at Fallingwater; People Traveling on a Train, Prints (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - People at Retirement Parties; People at Christmas Parties, About 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - People at Retirement Parties; People at Christmas Parties, About 2000; Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - People, Streamkeepers, Prints (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Peregrine Falcons, Banding, Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Peregrine Falcons, Gulf Building Nest and Banding, Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Peregrine Falcons, KDKA-TV Channel 2, 5:00PM News, June 7, 2002; Video (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Photos from Mo to B-Man, Prints (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Photos from Thomas E. Wiley, Prints (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Picnicking, Prints (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Polaroids of Paintings, Prints (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Rhododendron Festival, July 1986; Prints, Negatives, and Slides (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Skiing, Prints (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Spring Picnic, 1999; Prints (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Staff, Between 1955-1985 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Staff, Between 1955-1985; Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Staff, Alone and Group Shots, Prints (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Staff, Awards and Meetings, Between 1955-1985; Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Staff Christmas Party, 1997; Prints (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Staff Event, 1997; Prints (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Staff Outings, Between 1955-1985; Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Staff, Studio Portraits, Between 1955-1970; Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Swimming, Prints (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Tom's Run Outing, Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Volunteer Luncheon, 1999; Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Valentine's Day Hike at Bear Run, Prints (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Wildflower Walk, Prints (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - WPC Logos, Prints and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 31)